fashalot.com 2017-06-06

# Fashalot Privacy Policy - Fashalot.com

Last Modified: February 8th, 2017

Fashalot makes your shopping experience delightful and rewarding. We at Fashalot helps you discovery Fashion stores near you, their in-store offers, latest collection, and rewards you everytime you walk-in, shop, rate, follow or refer a friend. The rewards are in form of F-Cash. Every F-Cash is equal to Re.1 and can be redeemed for further shopping from F-Cash Partner stores or any free gift. When you use Fashalot you’ll share some information with us. We get that can affect your privacy. So we want to be upfront about the information we collect, how we use it, whom we share it with, and the choices we give you to control, access, and update your information. That’s why we’ve written this Privacy Policy. And it’s why we’ve tried to write it in a way that’s blissfully free of the legalese that often clouds these documents. Of course, if you still have questions about anything in our Privacy Policy, just contact us. 

There are three basic categories of information we collect:

  * Information you choose to give us
  * Information we get when you use our services
  * Information we get from third parties

Here’s a little more detail on each of these categories

When you interact with our service, we collect the information that you choose to share with us. For example, Fashalot require you to set up a basic Fashalot account, so we need to collect a few important details about you, such as: your mobile number, your name, your gender with which we can personalize your app experience. To make it even more personalized, you may yourself add a profile pictures of yours on the app. Of course, you’ll also provide us whatever information you send through the service, such as Lookbook Picture for earning F-Cash and get popular, your phonebook access for referring and gifting your contacts, location and notification access. It probably goes without saying, but we’ll say it anyway: When you contact Fashalot Support or communicate with us in any other way, we’ll collect whatever information you volunteer.

When you use our service, we collect information about which of those services you’ve used and how you’ve used them. We might know, for instance, that you just visited a particular location or store. Here’s a fuller explanation of the types of information we collect when you use our services :

  * **Usage Information.**  We collect information about your activity through our app. For example, we may collect information about:
  * how you interact with the service, such as fashion store discovery through different pages, visiting and purchase pattern, searches, referring friends, participating in contests on app etc.
  * **Content Information.**  We collect information about the content you provide, such as photo’s for lookbook section, bill uploads of your shopping for F-Cash earnings, redemption at stores or for mobile recharges, vouchers of movies, grocery, fashion etc. 
  * **Device Information.**  We collect device-specific information, such as the hardware model, operating system version, advertising identifier, unique application identifiers, unique device identifiers, browser type, language, wireless network, and mobile network information (including the mobile phone number). 
  * **Device Phonebook.**  When you sign-up on Fashalot, we ask you to give access to your phone contact list. On confirming, we take the contact list of your phone only to allow you to refer the app, inform your contacts to also benefit from Fashalot when they download and shop the using the app. In case you dont want to allow the contact, please dis-allow the access of contact. 
  * **Phone Access.**  In our app we have added our customer support phone number and email to reach us. You can directly call our customer support or email us from Fashalot App itself. 
  * **Camera and Photos.**  Many of our services require us to collect images and other information from your device’s camera and photos. This is solely when you intend to upload your profile picture, picture for Lookbook section or your shopping bill picture for earning F-Cash. For example, you won’t be able to process F-Cash for shopping unless we can access your camera or photos. 
  * **Location Information.**  We use location information to show you stores near you, their offers and in-store collection etc. When you use our services we may collect information about your location. With your consent, we may also collect information about your precise location using methods that include GPS, wireless networks, cell towers, Wi-Fi access points, and other sensors, such as gyroscopes, accelerometers, and compasses. 
  * **Information Collected by Cookies and Other Technologies.  ** We and our partners may use various technologies to collect and store information when you visit our service, and this may include using cookies or similar technologies to identify your browser or device. We may also use such technologies to receive, store and share information when you use Fashalot at our partners, such as advertising services, third-party applications or Fashalot features that may appear on other sites.

We may collect information that other users provide about you when they use our services. For example, if another user allows us to collect information from their device phonebook—and you’re one of that user’s contacts—we may combine the information we collect from that user’s phonebook with other information we have collected about you. We may also obtain information from other companies that are owned or operated by us, or any other third-party sources, and combine that with the information we collect through our services.

What do we do with the information we collect? The short answer is: Provide you with an amazing set of products and services that we relentlessly improve. Here are some of the ways we do that:

  * develop, operate, improve, deliver, maintain, and protect our products and services.
  * send you communications, including SMS, Notifications. For example, we may use SMS to inform you about your cashback credit, offers and deal, about your F-Cash balance and increase in benefits. You can always opt-out of receiving these SMS and in-App Notifications by writing to us at feedback@fashalot.com 
  * monitor and analyze trends and usage.
  * personalize the services by, among other things, or customizing the content we show you, including offers, new collection, cashbacks you can earn when you shop from your near by stores using Fashalot.
  * contextualize your experience by, among other things, using your precise location data (if, of course, you’ve consented to us collecting that data) and applying other labels based on the content.
  * improve targeting and measurement, including through the use of your precise location data (again, if you’ve consented to us collecting that data). 
  * verify your identity and prevent fraud or other unauthorized or illegal activity.
  * use information we’ve collected from cookies and other technology to enhance the services and your experience with them.
  * enforce our Terms of Service and other usage policies.

We may also store some information locally on your device. For example, we may store information as local cache so that you can open the app and view content faster.

We may share information about you, your shopping preference, your location etc with our business partners so that they can reach you with their exclusive offers and updates.  
We may share your information, with third parties like:

  * With service providers, sellers, and partners. We may share information about you with sellers that provide their virtual store fronts, offers and updates through our app, and business partners that provide services and functionality.
  * With third parties for legal reasons. We may share information about you if we reasonably believe that disclosing the information is needed to: 
    * comply with any valid legal process, governmental request, or applicable law, rule, or regulation.
    * investigate, remedy, or enforce potential Terms of Service violations.
    * protect the rights, property, and safety of us, our users, or others.
    * detect and resolve any fraud or security concerns.
  * With third parties as part of a merger or acquisition. If InnoTarget Fashalot Retail Pvt. Ltd. (Fashalot) gets involved in a merger, asset sale, financing, liquidation or bankruptcy, or acquisition of all or some portion of our business to another company, we may share your information with that company before and after the transaction closes.

We may also store some information locally on your device. For example, we may store information as local cache so that you can open the app and view content faster.

The services may also contain third-party links and search results, include third-party integrations, or offer a co-branded or third-party-branded service. Through these links, third-party integrations, and co-branded or third-party-branded services, you may be providing information (including personal information) directly to the third party, us, or both. You acknowledge and agree that we are not responsible for how those third parties collect or use your information. As always, we encourage you to review the privacy policies of every third-party website or service that you visit or use, including those third parties you interact with through our services.

We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time. But when we do, we’ll let you know one way or another. Sometimes, we’ll let you know by revising the date at the top of the Privacy Policy that’s available on our website and mobile application. Other times, we may provide you with additional notice (such as adding a statement to our websites’ homepages or providing you with an in-app notification).
